

Javier Olivieri

WORDPRESS DEVELOPER Y UX/UI DESIGNER

I am a Wordpress Developer with extensive experience in the design, implementation and administration of said CMS. I have great communication skills, I am detailed and creative. I enjoy working as a team and keep myself updated with the latest trends in the IT industry.

CONTACT

 \bigvee

coderjav@gmail.com

(a)

Cel: 1169658937



linkedin.com/in/coderman

ACADEMIC TRAINING

- Pharmacist, Buenos Aires' University, 2012.
- Front End Developer, Coderhouse, 2022.
- Full Stack Developer, Coderhouse, 2022.
- Ux/Ui Design, Coderhouse, 2022.

OTHER KNOWLEDGE

- Html, Css, JavaScript, Sass, Git, Github, Responsive Design, Bootstrap, Netlify, Vercel, Localwp, Git Bash, Google Font, Visual Studio Code.
- Figma, Behance, Elevator Pitch, Userflow, Usability, Accessibility, MVP, Whimsical.

LANGUAGES

• Intermediate English language

WORK EXPERIENCE

Web Developer, Wordpress

Decimo Technology Solutions (Costa Rica), March 2022 - present.

- Development of sites in Wordpress (Elementor, Wp Bakery, Custom).
- Constant communication with clients, to carry out the design.
- Development of promotional coupons for the GSK laboratory (Honduras, Costa Rica, Guatemala).
- Websites maintenance.
- Set up advertising and SEO campaigns.

Wordpress Developer (Front and Back)

Freelance, June 2021 - present.

- WooCommerce development.
- Translation of sites into several languages.
- Construction with Elementor, Wp Bakery, Divi.
- Search engine optimization.
- · Hosting.
- Site security.

Director of the Oncology sector and Head of pharmacy

Comei Pharmacy, November 2012 - September 2021

- Primary responsible for oncological treatments and medication. Contact with suppliers.
- Responsible for the pharmacy staff (6 people). Performance evaluation and personal growth.